passionforsavings.com 2013-12-17

# Privacy Policy -

**Privacy Policy:**

**1\. User’s Acknowledgment and Acceptance of Terms  
**

This Privacy Policy discloses the online privacy practices for Mile51 Media, LLC. and its affiliates including Passion for Savings® (collectively, “Passion for Savings®”) and applies to the information we collect through www.passionforsavings.com (the “Site”) and incorporates the Site’s Terms of Use. By accessing and/or using the Site, you are consenting to the collection, storage, and disclosure of data as described in this Privacy Policy.

BY COMPLETING THE REGISTRATION PROCESS AND/OR USING THIS site, YOU AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT WISH TO BE BOUND BY THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE EXIT THE site NOW. YOUR REMEDY FOR DISSATISFACTION WITH THIS site, OR ANY PRODUCTS, SERVICES, CONTENT, OR OTHER INFORMATION AVAILABLE ON OR THROUGH THIS site, IS TO STOP USING THE site AND/OR THOSE PARTICULAR PRODUCTS OR SERVICES. YOUR AGREEMENT WITH US REGARDING COMPLIANCE WITH THIS PRIVACY POLICY BECOMES EFFECTIVE IMMEDIATELY UPON COMMENCEMENT OF YOUR USE OF THIS site.

**2\. Modification.   **The site reserves the right, at any time, to modify, alter, update, or remove portions of this Privacy Policy. We will post any changes to this Policy on this page so you can readily review the most current version. We will alert you that changes have been made by indicating on the bottom of this Privacy Policy the date it was last updated.

**3\. Your IP Address**.  An Internet Protocol (IP) address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer every time you browse the Internet. When a user requests a page from the Site, our servers log the user’s current IP address. We use IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our servers and to administer the Site.

**4\. Cookies**.  The Site is developed using Active Server Pages (ASP), and we use per-session “cookies” (pieces of data your browser stores in your computer’s memory at Passion for Savings®’ request) to establish user sessions on our server. We use the cookies to carry information about usage from page to page through the Site. Passion for Savings® does not use cookies to retrieve personal information about you from your computer.

**5\. Acceptance of Cookies**.  Most browsers are set up to accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser settings to refuse them. If you disable cookies, your browser may experience some erratic behavior on some portions of the Site.

**6\. Disclosures to Third-Parties**. Passion for Savings® will not disclose your Submission Information to third parties, including, without limitation, Affiliates, advertisers, or marketing firms unless it is for the sole reason of disclosing Winner Email or physical address for shipment of a Prize.

**7\. Links**.  This Privacy Policy applies only to information collected by Passion for Savings®. Other Web sites (including those that we may link to) may have their own policies. Passion for Savings® has no responsibility for or control over the information-collection practices of such third-party Web sites.

**8\. Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisement**s. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

**9\. How to Contact Us**.  If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please e-mail us at heather@passionforsavings.com.

Last Updated: August 21, 2012
